Well, Oscar, congratulations, man. Let's
just start easy. Just uh what's what's
tonight been like for you and how's it
feel to be a New Orleans Saint?
>> Man, it's been a roller coaster. Um got
a lot of family, a lot of friends here,
but I'm I'm so blessed and so excited.
Can't wait to get there. Um you know,
got some my uh like my close family. Uh
my aunt, my uncle are from Louisiana, so
I've been up there a good bit. So, I'm
just really excited to get down there
and can't wait to get to work.
>> I know you've been here for uh for
games, but how much time have you spent
in New Orleans?
Not much really just for uh for a couple
the two Sugar Bowls I've been to and
both times I've left saying next time
I'm here. I was I was telling coach next
time I'm here. Uh the whole process I'm
I'm winning. So I'm excited.
>> How have those How did those
conversations go meeting with Saint
>> they were great. Um you know it was
actually pretty funny during the combine
uh interview process. because I had a
formal interview with them and the time
on my schedule was different than
theirs. So, I was waiting around and
they called me and I thought I was late
but it was just miscommunication. So, I
was freaking out going in there.
Luckily, I was right outside the room
though. But, um it was a great meeting.
I really enjoyed everyone there. They
were awesome and you know I I really
enjoyed it.
>> Hey, what does he add to the family?
>> I I'll ask them in a little bit but I
mean I couldn't exactly tell you but I
know they're very they're probably about
an hour and a half from New Orleans.
Oscar, do you feel like you have some
untapped skills or untapped production
that you want you want to see come to
fruition?
>> For sure. I mean, I think that um you
know, I'm a dude that can do it all and
that's why I'm so excited to to play
here. Um you know, whether it's special
teams, anywhere on offense, I'm a dude
that can bring anything to the table and
I think I've shown that over the past
couple years and I'm just excited to,
you know, play and win some games.
>> Oscar, you we talked to Christian. Did
you talk to Christian about the you
being selected as well?
>> That was the first call I answered right
after. Um answered his FaceTime. It was
awesome. Love that dude. I've known
Chris since
8th grade. And uh it it's crazy just
seeing it all all come to life and stuff
we've talked about and joked about. And
I mean, you know, we've probably been
out there during the Super Bowl week
saying, "No, we're both ending up in New
Orleans as just joking around." And you
know, to be able to go there with him
and go through this process with him,
like I wouldn't want to do it with
anyone else. talk to Christian playing
for Kirby and playing in the SEC. How
did that prepare you for this?
>> Um, Coach Smart, it's it's a it's a pro
program. That's just how it is. Um, I
talk you talk to any of those dudes that
leave and um, they leave prepared, they
leave ready. And, um, just the way that
he prepares us and, you know, gets you
ready for the next level. That's why I
went to Georgia. I knew I was going to
get developed and I knew he was going to
play against the best. And you can see
all the dudes on our team every day,
year in year out. And um you know it
just sets you up for success.
>> You uh you know anything about Tyler
Shuck? Watch any videos? Do any research
since you did talk to the Saints?
>> Oh yeah. I mean I've been watching him
since last year. I mean he's a baller.
Um you know he's one of the first people
that texted me. Um super excited to be
able to play with him. I mean he's an
elite quarterback and you know it's
going to be a lot of fun.
>> Oscar, what do you like about the uh the
tight end position? Played at a high
level, you know, with it since high
school. just being able to do it all.
Um, you know, tight ends I feel like are
the big biggest mismatches on the field.
Um, every team that's elite has an elite
tight end. And, you know, when you got a
good one, you can almost revolve the
offense around them and do crazy things.
And just to be able to be in a position
where I can flex out and run routes and
then put my hand in the dirt and block
on the on the offensive line is, you
know, there's nothing better than that.
So, I just, it's my favorite position. I
think it's one of the best positions you
can play. How do you think your uh
background in lacrosse helped you for
football and you find anything that
translated?
>> Um I think just you know the change of
direction they I feel like I'm a very
athletic guy and just being able to do
that and growing up playing a physical
fast sport like toughness is one of the
biggest things. I mean there's not many
sports where you can just run around up
and down the field and whack people with
metal sticks. So it was a ton of fun
growing up playing that. Was there a
tight end growing up that you watched as
you kind of modeled your style effort?
I
>> mean, there's been a bunch of them. Um,
you know, Greg Olsen was a great a dude
I loved watching growing up. Tony
Gonzalez just growing up in Georgia, but
um, you know, I really just like to look
at all these tight ends everywhere and
just model all their games. Um, I think
right now there's a lot of great dudes
in the league. Um, watching Kelsey
obviously and you know, being able to
play next to Bowowers, like just dudes
like that that are just now trending is
is awesome.
Uh you've talked a little bit about
having, you know, untapped potential
with the tight end position and and your
your time in the tight end position.
What did you learn about and what do you
like about the way that the Saints
utilize tight ends?
>> I mean, it's an explosive offense. I
think uh the Saints, you know, do it
better than, you know, a lot of the
teams in the NFL. Just being able to
move those guys all around and, you
know, having a dude like Jawan Johnson
out there running around and just, you
know, ballers. So, I think it's an
amazing offense to be a part of. I can't
wait to get there and get to work and,
you know, show these coaches and the
teammates what I can do to earn their
trust.
>> I saw where uh correct me if I'm wrong.
I think is like a suburb of of
Atlanta, right?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Were you a Falcons fan and maybe kind of
realized that that part of your life may
be over now?
>> I mean, to be honest, I was never really
a Falcons fan growing up in Georgia.
Like, I was a college football fan. It's
it's weird, you know, down here. It's
not like that where people grow up dieh
hard Falcons fans. Uh it's it's you're a
Georgia Bulldog fan growing up down
here. So, um I grew up watching college
football. Uh obviously I watched the
Falcons here and there, but you know, I
was never losing sleep over them.
>> Yeah. Oscar, how would you just kind of
describe your mentality as a as a
blocker? You kind of just described as
like the you playing a lot of why in in
that offense there like what's your
approach in that area of your game?
Yeah, I mean, um, I think it's the most
important thing you can do as a tight
end is be able to block and bring that
to your game. Um, I love just being able
to dominate another man and, um, in a
successful offense, you have a tight end
that could usually dominate the
perimeter and own the C gap. So, I take
pride in it and I enjoy it.
>> You said you've known Christian since
8th grade. How did y'all cross paths
prior to Georgia,
>> man? Just camps everywhere. Um, in high
school we went to the some camps
together and played in the All-American
Bowl together and he's always been a
character. You know, everyone in Georgia
always plays against each other at some
point and crosses paths at some point.
So, it's been awesome and uh, you know,
we've been very close friends ever since
you got to Georgia.
>> What was your best memories in the Sugar
Bowl? Y'all spent some time here. Did
you get a chance to kind of experience
the city a little bit?
Yeah, I mean just being on Bata, you
know, um just walking around like
I guess since it's a big bowl game,
there are a lot of Georgia fans
everywhere there, but the streets were
always alive, fans so passionate.
Um even though it's a Georgia game, like
you still see all the Saints fans
everywhere and everyone was walking
around. Um Trevor ET's a good buddy of
mine who's from there and he was kind of
showing me around everything and all the
food and I'm excited to eat some of that
food down there. So it's it's going to
be a great place. You know anything
about uh Jordan Tyson?
>> Oh yeah, I do. He's a baller. Trained
out there with him in uh um Arizona for
the past couple months and uh you know
he's a baller. Great dude to be around.
Great kid. Super funny, super awesome.
Uh I've only got to hang out with him
for a couple months, but I feel like we
got a bond already.